so beyond the last one which was the
online tree which is baby in a little
judgmental having a app and online with
people involved or not having other
people involved that walks you through
conflict management I think this is
something I'm good at but not
necessarily go to Doc's key and asking
permission to do which is as a middle
child I'm really good at pointing on the
other side of being like oh but did you
think that your spouse maybe meant this
and let's look it's like you made that
mean this negative thing but maybe it
could be sponged mean this positive
thing and if I was in their boat yeah I
would do that too it can be helpful if
someone's in the right space for that
that's why asking for permission is
probably a good call and I'm getting
better at that but in online conflict
management apps so that like you can
minimize the conflict in your life and
there could be two ways one of which is
if you're both involved in it like okay
we're having a fight let's go through
this app and you know more spouses and
we're trying to find out we're trying to
be more loving and caring for each other
and a way to deal with that or not but
then also if it's one-sided so like I
really dislike my coworker and I want to
find a way to not feel seething hatred
every time I see them and so like the
one-sided ones with the other person's
not involved in actual conflict
management you just have to deal with
your internal conflict and an app that
deals with conflict between people and
building relationships that is Apple
number 30 30 52 I don't even know what
decade